okay this is my training facility um
this is Jean's house I train here with
Charles Staley there's
Charles um here we've got the reverse
hyper which also serves as our kind of
countertop we've got reverse hyper there
so we do reverse hypers you can also get
underneath and do pendulum quadrip hip
extensions and Donkey kicks here we've
got all our specialty barbells so we've
got an axle bar a X
bar safety squat bar rackable camber Bar
Buffalo Bar all sorts of goodies and
down there that's a
Grappler okay we've got bumper plates
there's a little deadlift
lever uh this barbell that's a thick
barbell and that's an Olympic Bar with
more Flex so that one doesn't Flex at
all and this one flexes a
lot okay lot of different goodies over
there accessory things
power rack number
one with monkey chin
bar there we've got like a step up
attachment dips dip handles box squat
this little piece of rubber is like an
inch thick we stand on it to do deficit
deadlifts Power rck number two that's
like a some customade mono mono lift
apparatus thingy there um Power rck
number three we've got the equalizer in
there to do inverted
rows uh that's an adjustable incline
bench competition bench press right
there um different accessories some
cardi equipment that never gets used
this here is a scorcher to work the
glutes glute ham
developer with band
pegs uh we've got a leg extension leg
curl machine right
here uh wide base Sumo base 45° hyper
band Peg
attachments this here is a lever
[Music]
Squat
and easy curl bar tricep extension
machine heavy ass kettle bells uh
sitting on some pulling stands sometimes
we'll stand on the pulling stands and do
uh like straight leg deadlift with the
with the heavy kettle bell but that's a
92 kg kettle bell
that's a uh that so that one weighs 203
lb this one weighs 106
lb um more kettle
bells right
here dumbbells all the way up to 130s I
believe uh military press bench and like
a little lap pull down machine and
there's Charles
again that's about it so that's training
facility number one